A vacation to die for.
Club Dread is a comedy, horror, mystery film directed by Jay Chandrasekhar.
When a serial killer interrupts the fun at the swanky Coconut Pete's Coconut Beach Resort -- a
hedonistic island paradise for swingers --- it's up to the club's staff to stop the violence ...
or at least hide it!
Lars, played by Kevin Heffernan.
Putman, played by Jay Chandrasekhar.
Jenny, played by Brittany Daniel.
Coconut Pete, played by Bill Paxton.
Juan, played by Steve Lemme.
Penelope, played by Jordan Ladd.
Club Dread (also known as Broken Lizard's Club Dread) is a 2004 comedy slasher film directed by Jay Chandrasekhar and written by and starring the
comedy troupe Broken Lizard, Chandrasekhar, Kevin Heffernan, Steve Lemme, Paul Soter, Erik Stolhanske, Brittany Daniel, and Bill Paxton.
The film follows a group of staff members on a tropical island
resort, where an unknown killer begins a murder spree.
It's an international co-production film between the United States and Mexico.
Though the story is set on an island in Costa
Rica, filming took place in Mexico.
Club Dread was released on February 27, 2004, and grossed $7.6 million at the box
office on a budget of $8.6 million, becoming a financial failure.
The film received mixed-to-negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of island, machete, beautiful
woman, serial killer, slasher spoof.
The tone is intense and lighthearted and dark.